準備好了嗎
All set?
-你要去之後的派對嗎  -可能吧
- Are you going to the after party? - Maybe.
那或許我們在那見
Well, maybe I'll see you there.
-你叫什麼  -伊茜
- What's your name? - Issy.
你能看到他嗎
Can you see him?
-吧檯邊黑白夾克的那人  -對
- White and black jacket by the bar? - Yeah.
你幹什麼  你幹什麼
What are you doing? What are you doing?!
媽
Mum?
-你幹了什麼  -我警告過你  克裡斯申
- What have you done? - I warned you, Christian.
你幹了什麼
What have you done?!
在我們死之前
第一集
兩年後
你在想什麼
What you thinking about?
事情
Stuff.
可能永遠不會發生  你知道嗎
It might never happen, you know?
-你保證嗎  -嗯
- Do you promise? - Yeah.
我保證
I promise.
喂
Oi?
那是給尼克生日的
That's for, Nick's birthday.
我還在想我們要慶祝什麼呢
I wondered what we were celebrating.
慶祝  更像是借酒澆愁吧
Celebrating? More like drowning my sorrows.
天吶  是今天嗎
Oh, Christ. Is that today?
你確定那是她想談的嗎
You sure it's what she wants to talk about?
她已經幾個月沒跟我說話了  突然之間
She's barely spoken to me for months and now, suddenly,
她想敘敘舊
she wants to have a catch up.
或許這樣也好
Well, maybe it's for the best.
我不想調任  他們怎麼就不能
I don't want a bloody transfer. Why can't they just give me
給我個好案子  然後別來煩我了
a decent case and leave me alone?
我是指對我們
I meant for us.
伊茜  草字頭的茜
Issy with an S.
-是工作  -小三的小三
- It's a work thing. - The other, other woman.
她是個線人
She's a contact.
肖恩  我開玩笑的  我最好不知道
Sean, I'm teasing. It's better that I don't know.
你不用告訴我任何事
You don't need to tell me anything.
或許我該告訴你
Maybe I do, actually.
-什麼意思  -現在不行  我們已經遲了
- What do you mean? - Not now. We're late as it is.
-你不跟我一起去嗎  -不  我得回趟家
- Aren't you coming in with me? - No, I need to pop home.
-海倫今天回來嗎  -對
- Oh, is Helen coming back today? - Yeah.
我應該至少努力
I should at least try and
讓人覺得我住在那裡
make it look like I've been living there.
回見
See you.
對
'Yeah.
我把床弄亂了  搞髒了一些盤子
'I've unmade the bed, dirtied some dishes.'
-你來局裡嗎  -不  我要去克利夫頓見人
- Are you heading in? - 'No, I'm meeting someone in Clifton.
聽著  我之前是真心的
'Listen, I meant what I said.'
什麼  關於你的線人嗎
What, about your contact?
關於他們想跟你談調任的事
'About them wanting to talk to you about the transfer.
這樣或許真的不錯
'It really might be for the best.'
怎麼會
How come?
也許這是個標誌
'Well, maybe it's a sign
你應該考慮提前退休
you should be thinking of early retirement.
我也該這麼做
'And I should too.'
怎麼  你想離開警局嗎
What - are you thinking about leaving the force?
對  還有我妻子
'Yeah, and my wife as well.'
-你確定嗎  -我想自由  漢娜
- Are you sure? - 'I want to be free, Hannah.
能自由地跟你在一起
'Free to be with you.
照顧你  給你買東西
'To..To take care of you, to buy you things,
比如昂貴的威士忌
'like, expensive bottles of scotch...'
和美麗的黑裙子
..And beautiful black dresses.
你  你喝那酒了嗎
Have you - have you been at that bottle?
如果我們...
'Hey, if we...'
肖恩
Sean?
肖恩  你在嗎
Sean, are you there?
我是肖恩  現在無法接電話
'Hi, this is Sean. I can't take your call,
請留言
please leave a message.'
你有出色的履歷  漢娜
You've got an exemplary record, Hannah.
你無需再證明什麼
You've got nothing left to prove.
-漢娜  -嗯  什麼
- Hannah? - Yeah..Yes?
-你在聽我說話嗎  -對  對
- Are you even listening to me? - Um, yeah, yeah.
當然  你說這不是針對個人
Of course. Uh, you said that it wasn't personal.
確實不是
Well, it's not.
我知道這聽上去像文職
I know it probably sounds like a bit of a desk job,
但到了你這個年紀
but at this stage of your career
或許這不是壞事
perhaps that isn't such a bad thing.
漢娜
Hannah?
抱歉  我只是在想
Sorry, erm, I was just wondering,
-你今早有肖恩的消息嗎  -沒有
- have you heard from Sean at all this morning? - No.
為什麼這麼問
Why do you ask?
只是我想他這會該回來了
It's just that I thought that he'd be back by now.
從哪裡回來
Back from where?
他說他要去見線人
He said that he was meeting a contact.
他告訴你的嗎
He told you that?
對  今天早上
Yeah. Yeah. This morning.
他不需要保姆  漢娜
He doesn't need a baby-sitter, Hannah.
不  不不  當然不
No. No, no, of course not.
我們還是關注下手頭的東西吧
Let's focus on the matter in hand.
我是肖恩  現在無法接電話
'Hi, this is Sean. I can't take your call,
請留言
please leave a message.'
你好
Hello.
好  謝謝  沒事
OK, thank you, that's OK.
沒事
Fine.
沒有嗎  好  謝謝你們抽出時間  拜
No? OK. Thanks for your time, bye-bye.
我是肖恩  現在無法接電話
'Hi, this is Sean. I can't take your call,
請留言
please leave a message.'
肖恩  是我
Sean, erm, it's me.
聽著  現在我擔心了  你能給我回電嗎  拜
Look, I, I'm worried now. Will you call me back? Bye.
美麗的黑裙子
'..Beautiful black dresses...'
早上好
Hi, good morning.
抱歉打擾  我想問問
Sorry to bother you. Erm, I was just wondering,
你今天早上是否看到
did you happen to see a blue Volvo
一輛藍色沃爾沃停在店外
parked outside the shop this morning?
九點過後嗎
Shortly after nine?
對  差不多那時候
Uh, yeah, that sounds about right.
我不知道是不是沃爾沃
I don't know if it was a Volvo,
-但肯定是藍色  -你怎麼注意到的
- but it was definitely blue. - And what made you notice it?
我一開始沒有  是司機引起了我的注意
I didn't at first. It was the driver who caught my attention.
那是為什麼
Oh, what was the reason for that?
他站在櫥窗外好久
He was stood outside the window for ages,
盯著那條裙子
staring at that dress.
好吧
Ok.
這是他嗎
Is that him?
我願意堵上一切他肯定會買那裙子
I'd have bet anything he was going to come in and buy it.
通常你能看出來
You can usually tell the type.
-那他為什麼沒買  -不知道  之後我再看時
- So, what stopped him? - I don't know. Next time I looked,
他站在車旁  那時我才發現車是藍色
he was standing by his car. That's when I noticed it was blue.
之後他開走了嗎
And, then he just drove off?
說不好  有輛灰色貨車擋住了我的視線
Couldn't tell you, this grey van stopped and blocked my view,
等那車開走後  藍色的車也不見了
and, by the time it moved, the car was gone.
好  謝謝
OK, thank you.
你想好是否買這裙子了嗎
Have you made up your mind on the dress?
那地方全是攝像頭
There are cameras all over that part of town.
-有人能檢查一下監控嗎  -我來
- Can someone check through the footage? - I'll do it.
謝謝  瑞秋
Thanks, Rachel.
馬庫斯  芙蘭  達裡斯  你們去挨家挨戶問詢吧
Marcus, Fran, Darius, will you go door to door?
-行  -好
- Sure. - Yeah.
我們要讓巡警幫忙嗎
Should we get uniform to help?
先不要告訴別人  可能是白忙一場
Let's keep this to ourselves - could be a wild goose chase.
你有什麼要補充的嗎
Anything you'd like to add?
比利  你有空嗎
Billy, have you got a moment?
幹得好
Well done.
為了什麼
For what?
找到那個目擊者  有點大海撈針
For finding that witness - bit of a needle in a haystack.
也不是
Not really.
得了吧  漢娜  你就恰好找到了
Oh, come on, Hannah. You just happened to make a beeline
克利夫頓今早唯一看到肖恩的人嗎
to the one person in Clifton who noticed Sean this morning?
顯然還有其他事你沒告訴我
There's clearly something you're not telling me.
算了  比利  這無關緊要
Leave it, Billy. It's not material.
那我來這幹什麼
So...why am I here?
肖恩告訴了漢娜一個線人
Sean told Hannah about a contact.
你最近一直在跟他合作
You've been working with him recently.
我想如果她告訴你
I thought it might help
他所說的  你或許能幫上忙
if she talked you through what he told her.
他的線人叫伊茜
His contact is called Issy.
等等
Hang on.
他告訴你名字了
He told you her name?
不算是吧  是個意外
Uh, not exactly. It was an accident.
他還說什麼了
Well, what else did he tell you?
幾乎沒說  但我很確信
Almost nothing, but I'm pretty sure
他正要去見她
that he was on his way to meet her.
但你不確定
But you're not certain?
他今早提到了她
Well, he mentioned her this morning.
但你今天早上怎麼和肖恩在一起
But why were you with Sean this morning?
比利
Billy...
之後  我稍晚跟他聯繫時
And then, when I spoke to him again, later on,
他說要去克利夫頓見人
he said that he was meeting someone in Clifton,
然後我們的電話就被切斷了  突然切斷
and then our call got cut off, just like that.
-就這樣嗎  -對
- And that's it? - Yeah.
看看他最近的調查
Just take a look through his current investigations.
是否有異常的地方
See if anything stands out.
好
Ok.
跟漢娜合作
And work with Hannah on it.
你這懦夫
You fucking cowards.
現身吧  你這懦夫
Show yourselves, you fucking cowards.
來啊
Come on.
對  去那邊  我負責那裡
Yeah, yeah, go and do that way. I'm gonna go in there.
我想問問你是否在這附近
I was just wondering if you've seen
-見過一輛藍色沃爾沃  -沒有  我沒看到
- a blue Volvo around here. - No, I ain't see anything.
我是埃文和薩默塞特警局警察
I'm from Avon and Somerset Police.
-不好意思  -好
- I'm sorry. - OK.
輸入密碼
好吧  伊茜
OK, Issy.
輸入密碼
一條新信息
你在哪
有消息嗎
Any luck?
聽著  我  我沒對你說實話
Look, I... I haven't been completely straight with you.
我在肖恩失蹤的那條街上找到了這個
I found this in the street where Sean went missing.
你為什麼認為這是他的
What makes you think it's his?
裡面有條來自伊茜的信息
There's a text message from Issy.
你為什麼沒告訴蒂娜
Why did you not tell Tina?
這不符合規矩  對吧  第二部手機
Well, it's hardly regulation, is it, a second mobile phone?
她不是個刻板的監工  知道嗎
She's not a complete jobsworth, you know.
如果只是照本宣科  坐不到她那個位置
You don't get as far as she has by doing everything by the book.
那我該怎麼辦
So, what do I do with it?
你想怎麼辦
What do you want to do?
我不知道  給她發信息
Well, I don't know. Text her?
看我是否能找到
See if I can find out anything
追蹤到肖恩的線索
that might help us track down Sean?
你不能  你不能在別人的調查中
You can't go... You can't go blundering blindly
盲目地胡亂摸索  漢娜
into someone else's investigation, Hannah.
誰說我是胡亂摸索了
Who says I'm blundering?
我們都不確定肖恩是否失蹤了
We don't know for certain if Sean is missing.
如果他明早進了這門
He won't thank us for scaring off a contact
他不會感謝我們嚇壞了線人
if he walks through that door tomorrow morning.
天吶  比利
For God's sake, Billy.
伊茜顯然不知道肖恩失蹤了
Issy clearly doesn't know that Sean is missing.
我可以假裝是他
I can just pretend to be him.
說不定  她能給我們一些線索
You never know, she might give us something to go on.
這場對話沒發生過
This conversation never happened.
你在哪
你自己找死
It's your funeral.
-漢娜  -你好  薩曼莎
- Hannah. - Hello, Samantha.
我沒記錯日子吧
I haven't got the wrong day?
不不  是今天  請進
No, no, it's today. Come in.
-你好嗎  -很好  很高興見到你
- How are you? - Very well. Nice to see you.
-我也是  你看上去真美  -謝謝
- Nice to see you too. You look very well. - Thank you.
生日快樂  尼克
Happy birthday, Nick.
漢娜  我不知道你被邀請了
Hannah! I didn't know you were invited.
我想這是那種雖然被邀請
Well, I think it was one of those invitations
-但不希望你去的場合  -胡說
- where you're not expected to show up. - Nonsense.
你好嗎
How are you?
老態龍鍾  筋疲力盡
Ancient, knackered.
雙胞胎讓我感覺自己老了
The twins make me feel my age.
-姑娘們讓你精力充沛嗎  -精力充沛
- Oh, the girls full of beans? - Full of beans.
這或許能讓你放鬆些
Hmm, this might take the edge off.
你不該破費的
You shouldn't have.
我不確定薩曼莎會贊同
I'm not sure that Samantha will approve.
所以我才喜歡
And that is why I love it.
你最近  你最近有他的消息嗎
Have you... Have you heard from him?
克裡斯申嗎  他在廚房
Christian? He's in the kitchen.
克裡斯申今晚來了嗎
Christian's here tonight?
他是我兒子  漢娜
He is my son, Hannah.
當然  我知道  只是
Well, of course, I know that. It's just...
去吧  你該跟他談談
Go on, you should speak to him.
我會的
I will.
這是你起碼能做的
It's the least you can do.
但別對他太嚴格
But go easy on him.
尼克  那才是問題  我們總是管太鬆
Nick, that's the problem. We always did.
你好嗎
How are you?
有煙嗎
Got any fags?
沒有
No.
你爸以前會在你的可可米裡面藏一些
Your dad used to hide some in your Coco Pops.
你只會找到麥片
You'll only find muesli in there.
找到了
Bingo.
-你工作了嗎  -跟你有關嗎
- Are you working? - What's it to you?
在餐廳
In a restaurant.
真不錯  我學生的時候
Oh, well, that's great. I used to love waiting on tables
-也喜歡在餐廳端盤子  -我是個洗碗工
- when I was a student. - Yeah, I'm a dish washer.
那也不錯
Well, that's good too,
只要他們能付你工資  讓你自給自足
as long as they're paying you enough to live on.
-對  還讓我不惹麻煩  -我不是這個意思
- Yeah, and keep me out of trouble. - That's not what I meant.
你接下來就要問我有沒有交稅了
You'll be asking if I'm paying my taxes next.
克裡斯申
Christian...
他們對我很好
They're good to me.
我為你開心
I'm pleased for you.
那你呢  還在打擊小偷小販嗎
So, what about you? You still chasing petty criminals?
很快你就會給人開交通罰單了
You'll be handing out parking tickets before you know it.
那幸好你買不起車
Well, it's a good job you can't afford a car.
這房子不能吸煙
This is a no-smoking household.
交出來
Hand it over.
我在告訴大家快切蛋糕了
I've been told to tell everyone it is time for cake.
我們正要過去
We're just coming.
這酒真不錯  克裡斯申
This is a great wine, Christian.
我知道  你能信嗎
I know. Can you believe it?
是克羅地亞酒  從他餐廳拿的
It's Croatian, from his restaurant.
店主是克羅地亞人嗎
Oh, the owner's Croatian?
這些是我的嗎
Are these mine?
老天  別告訴薩曼莎
For God's sake, don't tell Samantha.
我很高興看到你過得不錯
I'm glad to know that you're doing OK,
在發生了那些事後
after what happened.
你是說在你幹的那些事後
You mean, after what YOU did!
見鬼
Fuck's sake.
你在找這個嗎
You looking for this?
我...想試試猜出他的密碼
I...thought I'd try and guess his password.
我早就想到了
I'm way ahead of you.
這合法嗎  比利
Oh, is that legit, Billy?
你告訴蒂娜了嗎
Did you tell Tina?
你很有趣  知道嗎
You've very funny, you know that?
你還為今晚打扮了一番
I see you've dressed for the occasion.
聽著  我覺得我們需要的一切
So, listen, I think that everything we need
都會在那台電腦上
we're going to find on that laptop.
你看了哪些文件  比利
Which file did you go into, Billy?
我先提前道歉  我做的咖啡很難喝
I apologise in advance. I make terrible coffee.
謝謝
Thank you.
你對肖恩有多瞭解
How well do you know Sean?
其實不瞭解
Not at all really.
他說在調查東歐的販毒集團
Said he was investigating an Eastern European drug connection,
咨詢了我的意見
asked my advice.
為什麼  那你是的專長嗎
Oh, why is that? Is that your speciality?
據說是的
Allegedly.
所以我被調派到了這裡
That's why I was seconded here.
從國家犯罪調查局嗎
Uh, from the National Crime Agency?
對
Aye.
在犯調局之前你在哪
So, where were you before the NCA?
你最好別問我那些
It's probably better you don't ask me that.
國家安全局嗎
Security services?
軍情五處
Mi5.
如果你想  可以讓我滾蛋
You can tell me to piss off if you want.
嗯  我可能會吧
Yeah, well, I might do.
但警察的兒子怎麼會
But how does the son of a police officer end up
因蓄意持毒坐牢21個月呢
serving 21 months for possession with intent?
那都是老黃歷了
It's an age-old story.
是個...痛苦的離婚
It's a...painful divorce,
爸爸組建了新家庭
Dad gets a new family,
媽媽有了探探賬號  然後
Mum gets a Tinder account and, um...
克裡斯申逐漸誤入歧途
..Christian gradually falls off the rails.
我也有過同樣的經歷  還有件T恤
Been there. Got the T-shirt.
探探賬號嗎
Tinder account?
不是
No.
痛苦的離婚
Painful divorce.
你有孩子嗎
Have you got kids?
有  16歲
Aye. 16-year-old.
恨死我了
Hates my guts.
你幹的事很硬核
That was pretty hardcore, what you did.
我...
Well, I...
我以為他能判個緩刑
I thought he'd get a suspended sentence.
一記警鐘嗎
A wake-up call?
如果沒有肖恩  事情會糟糕很多
It would've been so much worse without Sean.
他非常棒  挺身而出
He's been amazing. He stepped right up.
他每兩周去看克裡斯申一次
He visited Christian every couple of weeks, every week.
沒惹麻煩吧
Staying out of trouble?
當然
Yeah.
健身了嗎
Been working out?
能不那麼無聊
It relieves the boredom.
你收到我給你的錢了嗎
You get the money I sent?
-我會還給你  -不需要
- I'll pay you back. - No need.
但我會的
I-I will, though.
為一切
For everything.
你在法庭上力挺我  為我說話
The way you stood by me, spoke up for me in court.
所有人都會做一樣的事
Anyone would've done the same.
但他們沒有
Well, they didn't.
說真的
Seriously...
你適應得還行嗎
..Are you coping all right?
嗯
Yeah.
我交了個朋友  我們在照顧對方
I made a friend. We're looking out for each other.
那麼
So...
你接下去打算怎麼辦
..What are you going to do next?
抱歉
Sorry.
你說什麼
You were saying?
-算了  這能等  -不  接著說
- Forget it, it can wait. - No, go on.
我說你有什麼計劃
I asked what your plan was.
你打算怎麼賺錢
What you going to do for money?
別擔心  我都搞定了
Oh, don't worry, I'm all sorted.
我可以幫你找工作  知道嗎
I can take care of all of that for you, you know?
不需要
There's no need.
我之前跟你說的那個人
Uh, this guy I told you about,
斯特凡  他幫我找了工作
Stefan, he's got me a job.
你在監獄裡認識的毒販子
A dealer guy you met inside?
不是你想的那樣
It's not what you think.
是一家餐廳  洗盤子
It's in a restaurant, like, washing dishes.
你確定是正經餐廳嗎
And you're sure it's legit?
我很快就會知道了
I'll soon find out.
克拉伊納
Krajina.
Krajina!
克拉伊納
Krajina...
聽著像克羅地亞
That sounds Croatian.
嚴格來說是塞爾維亞克羅地亞語  但夠近了
Serbo-Croatian technically, but, close enough.
意思是"邊界"  或差不多的意思
It means "Frontier," I think, or something like that.
老天  比利
Oh, for God's sake, Billy.
別怪我啊  肖恩的文件裡到處都是這個
Don't shoot the messenger. This stuff is all over Sean's files.
以及一遍遍出現那個詞
And that word over and over again.
克拉伊納
Krajina.
你怎麼知道這語言
How come you recognise the lingo?
我前任和他家人逃離了內戰
My ex and his family fled the civil war.
他總想讓克裡斯申說那裡的話
He was always trying to get Christian to speak it.
那你呢
How about you?
我在那地方待過一陣
Oh, I spent a wee bit of time in that neck of the woods.
90年代嗎
In the '90s?
關於什麼
克拉伊納
抱歉搞得一團亂
Sorry about the mess.
來  多給你的
Here, a little bit extra.
不需要  那是我的工作
There's no need. That's my job.
繼續加油
Keep it up.
吃午飯了
Hey, lunch.
你好膽小
Wow. You're jumpy.
抱歉
Sorry.
他們不會吃了你
They won't eat you.
或許你該脫下...
Perhaps you should, um, take off the...
對
Right.
老兄  來坐吧
Hey, man. Come, sit.
歡迎來到飯桌  克裡斯申
Welcome to our table, Christian.
這是你第一次嗎
Is this your first time?
都怪你  媽
Shame on you, Mama.
這孩子都在這工作三個月了
The boy's been working here three months.
我想先確保他會留下來
I wanted to make sure he was staying first.
從今往後他跟我們一起吃
He'll eat with us from now on.
斯特凡
Stefan?
停在了工業區
好
飯桌上不談生意  拜託  達沃
Not at the table, please, Davor.
事發緊急
It's urgent.
你得去處理掉
我要怎麼找到
我給你發了信息
好
克裡斯申  把馬鈴薯餃子給我
他不說克羅地亞語
He doesn't speak Croatian.
你不是克羅地亞人嗎
What kind of Croat are you?
在英國土生土長  我媽媽是英國人
Born and bred in the UK, I'm afraid. My mum's English.
但你姓拉蒂奇
But your surname's Radic.
對  我爸好像是裡耶卡人
Yeah, my dad's from Rijeka, I think.
我祖母也是
Ah, so's my grandmother.
世界真小
Small world, hey.
我聽說你有個克羅地亞的紋身
I heard you have a Croatian tattoo.
那是斯特凡的主意
It was Stefan's idea.
證明我們一起蹲過號子  以及我們本是同根生
To show the time we served together and the roots we share.
你該去了
You should go.
現在嗎
Now?
對  現在  帶上克裡斯申
Yes, now. And take Christian.
讓他吃完
Let him finish.
晚點見
See you later.
謝謝
Thank you.
-來啊  -快快快
- Come on! - Go, go, go!
兩個月前
加油  你能跑多快  你能跑多快
Come on! What you got? What you got?
來啊
Come on.
不
No!
你不行了
Oh, you're losing it.
混蛋
Arsehole.
-對了  你之前說得對  -什麼事
- Yeah, you were right by the way. - About what?
那家餐廳
The restaurant.
絕對是什麼事的幌子
It's definitely a front for something.
真的嗎  你覺得是毒品嗎
Seriously? You think it's drugs?
還可能是什麼
What else would it be?
這家人不是我們的關注重點  肯定是小打小鬧
The family's not on our radar, must be pretty small-scale.
從我看到的不是
Not from what I've seen.
到處都有現金
There's cash everywhere.
那  趕緊離開那裡
So...get the hell out of there.
不  我要留下
No. I'm staying.
別犯傻
Don't be an idiot.
你負擔不起再趟一次那種渾水了
You can't afford to get mixed up with that shit again.
我不會的
I won't.
-我想也許  -也許什麼
- I thought maybe... - Maybe what?
我可以給你信息
I could feed you information.
什麼
What?
關於他們的計劃
About what they're up to.
幫你調查  拿下他們
Help you investigate, take them down.
絕不行
No fucking way.
你幾乎是家人  這樣不道德
You're practically family. It would be totally unethical.
甚至不合法
Illegal even.
聽著  他們不知道我能聽懂克羅地亞語
Look, they don't know I understand Croatian,
所以我可以偷聽  匯報給你
so I could listen in, report back.
他們開始相信我了
They're starting to trust me.
這是個爛主意
It's a terrible idea.
為什麼
Why?
很可能有危險
It could be dangerous.
你想證明什麼
What are you trying to prove?
我沒想證明任何事
I'm not trying to prove anything.
是因為漢娜嗎
Is this about Hannah?
不
No.
-果凍娃娃  -對
- Jelly Tots? - Yeah.
果凍娃娃怎麼了
What's wrong with Jelly Tots?
-不  只是...  -喂
- No, it's just... - Oi!
把你的髒手拿開
You keep your grubby hands off.
我們來這幹什麼
So, what we doing here?
你要幫我找一輛車
You're helping me recover a car.
什麼車
What kind of car?
需要消失的那種
The kind that needs to disappear.
為什麼
Why?
你問題真多
You ask a lot of questions.
你說過會教我訣竅
You said you'd show me the ropes.
有個傢伙  他在惹麻煩
There's a guy, he was causing trouble.
什麼人
Which guy?
你開這輛車  跟著我
You drive this one. Follow me.
你很安靜
在棄車
回復
藍色沃爾沃嗎
老兄  怎麼了  老兄
Hey, man. What's up, man?
-那人怎麼了  -消失了
- What happened to the guy? - Gone.
車走茶涼  什麼都沒了
The car's gone, he's gone, it's all gone.
來啊
Come on!
天吶
Oh, man.
怎麼了  老兄
What's up, man?
這太瘋狂了
This is mad!
我們走
Let's go.
了結他
Finish it.
藍色沃爾沃沒了
你是誰
我需要你的幫助
肖恩失蹤了
布里斯托機場
我需要跟你談談
I need to speak to you.
我在跟伊茜聯絡  肖恩的線人
I'm in touch with Issy, Sean's contact.
怎麼會
How on earth?
我在店外的街上找到了這部手機
I found this phone in the street outside the shop.
你之前怎麼沒告訴我
Why didn't you tell me before?
我現在告訴你了  他在用這個聯繫她
I'm telling you now. He's been using it to communicate with her.
你也是嗎
And so have you?
她知道我不是肖恩
She knows that I'm not Sean.
伊茜是我們唯一的線索
Issy was all we had to go on.
有人嗎
Hello?
看起來肖恩確實在監控這地方
Looks like Sean has definitely had this place under surveillance.
我去那吃過飯  在克利夫頓
I've eaten there. It's in Clifton.
我們在等什麼
So, what are we waiting for?
等等
Hang on.
-我們沒有搜查令  -或合理理由
- We don't have a warrant. - Or reasonable grounds.
但你肯定伊茜在那裡工作
But you definitely think that Issy works there?
我只知道肖恩在調查那裡
I only know it's on Sean's radar.
或許我們該去看看
Maybe we should take a look.
我們剛收到電話
We've just had a call.
有個被毒打的男人符合肖恩的外貌
There's a badly beaten man that fits Sean's description.
-在哪  -曼迪普斯
- Where? - The Mendips.
把那地方封鎖  趕緊
I want the site locked down - now.
來  喝點水
Come on, here.
再來點
Again.
-喂  -喂
- Hello? - Um, hello.
我叫漢娜  我是肖恩的同事
My name is Hannah, I'm a colleague of Sean's.
-我需要跟他談談  我能跟他說話嗎  -好
- I need to speak to him. Can I speak to him? - Yeah.
肖恩  是我  漢娜
Sean, it's me, it's Hannah.
我是漢娜
It's Hannah.
聽著  你得堅持住  我們很快就到
Listen, you've got to hold on. We're minutes away.
伊茜
Issy.
沒事  沒事
Yeah, it's OK. It's OK.
我知道伊茜
I know about Issy.
你得堅強點
You've got to be strong now.
堅持住  堅持住  肖恩  堅持住
Just hang on, just hang on, Sean. Please, stay with me.
我們快到了
We're nearly there.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
肖恩
Sean.
肖恩  肖恩
Sean? Sean!
武裝警察  快出來
Armed police! Show yourself.
-安全  -安全
- Clear. - Clear!
加油  挺住
Come on, come on.
收到
Copy.
狗找到了肖恩的腳印
The dogs have found Sean's trail.
他從西邊過來
He came from the west.
槍手呢
And the shooter?
他的腳印到處都是
His tracks are all over the place,
然後突然間  他轉身徑直朝這邊過來
until he suddenly turns and walks straight here.
也許他看到了什麼
Well, maybe he saw something?
或有人告訴他去哪裡找人
Or maybe someone told him where to look.
肖恩死了
新消息  來自伊茜
都是我的錯
幫我找出
幹這事的人
我不信任你
你不認識我
大家都知道  我們的一位同事失蹤了
As you know, one of our colleagues has been missing,
我很遺憾通知各位
and I regret to inform you that
今天我們失去了肖恩·哈達克
today we've lost Sean Hardacre.
這起案件現已成為謀殺案
This is now a murder investigation
我們會盡全力
and we will do everything in our power
找到兇手  或兇手們  將其繩之於法
to bring the killer, or killers, to justice.
漢娜
Hannah...
我們得告訴你一些事
..We have to tell you something.
我想我們中有內鬼
We believe we have a leak.
麥當娜紅酒餐廳
我願意為肖恩復仇
我會讓他們
付出代價
發送